wholikesu.net 2010-04-20

# Who likes you? - Online Dating Service.

**WhoLikesU** , Privacy Policy  
Your Privacy Rights  
Last Updated: August 9, 2009

This Privacy Policy is aimed at protecting the Privacy of our users and demonstrates that we respect the information you put on our website. Thereinafter, issues such as who is a user of our websites, the information we collect, how that information may be used, with whom it may be shared, and your choices about such uses and disclosures are explained.

Before using our website or services or making business with us we strongly recommend reading this Privacy Policy. By using our website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions about our privacy practices, please refer to the paragraph 13 of this Privacy Policy.

  1. What information the website needs?

Personally identifiable information (PII) and non-personally identifiable information (Non-PII) are needed for the proper work of the services. The information is collected when you registering on our website, using it or in some other manner.

  2. Profile information

The information, you put on our website, may be available for other users on our websites and in case when we send out newsletters to our users. Your profile is available for view on our Site, by both registered users and anonymous visitors who view our Site. Description, photos, age, city (country, Not your postal address) will be shown on your profile page for other users. **Your email address is confidential and will not be posted by us in your profile, newsletters or shared with third parties.** We dont include email address to your visible profile information. Refrain from putting your personal information on your visible profile. We cannot control who reads your posting or how other users can use that information. For example, if you post your email address, you may receive unsolicited messages.

  3. Cookies

We use data collection and persistence devices such as "cookies" on certain pages of our Site for practical purposes. "Cookies" are small files placed in memory and/or disk on your computer that assist us in providing customized services and better functionality as you move from page to page within our Site. Cookies make the personalization of your Internet experiences possible. For example, when you surf from page to page on our website, cookies help us to remember your login and password so that you dont need to log-in each time you click on someones page. For the proper functioning of our Services we need to know who you are and what actions have you taken in course of session.  

We also offer certain features that are only available through the use of cookie. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits; however, many aspects of our Service may not work properly without them.

  4. Web Beacons

We may use standard Internet tools, such as web beacons, which collect information that tracks your use of our website and enables us to customize our services and advertisements.  

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13.

  5. How We Use Your Information

By registering on our website you agree that we may use your personal information to improve our websites, to contact you and to deliver information to you regarding your account, newsletters and/or alerts for which you have confirmed opt-in and may cancel it at any time. All your e-mail addresses you provide are saved in our data base and are used only to contact you via e-mail in accordance with your preferences. We do not share your email address with any other users of our Site, including paid subscribers.  

If you do not wish to receive e-mails from our website, you may cancel your e-mail subscription anytime while creating or editing your user profile or by clicking link Change settings if you don't want to receive this email in the letters you receive. By accepting this Privacy Policy and not changing your notification preferences, you are expressing your agreement to receive this information. If you don't want to receive notification letters from our site go to the settings section of your account, choose "my notifications" and uncheck the boxes of those letters you dont want to receive. Finally, click on Save button to save the changes  

As a matter of policy, we do not sell or rent any PII about you to any third party.  

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website.   
These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.   
If you would like get more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_cookies.html)

  6. How can you access your personal information? 

If you have an account on our website, you can review and update your personal information online by logging into your account and clicking on your account settings.  
You can make your account inactive by visiting account cancellation in account settings or upon your notification. If your account is inactive we hide your account so nobody can see your account information.  

Nevertheless, your personal information will stay in our database for certain period of time, even after making your account inactive. We store your information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our terms and conditions. In some cases such prior information may never be completely removed from our databases due to technical and legal constraints, including stored 'back up' systems. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your Personal information will be completely removed from our databases in response to any request you may submit.

  7. Password safety

Full responsibility for your login information and password, including fees lays on you. Therefore, we do not recommend that you disclose your Site password or login information to any third party. If you choose to share this information with any third party, you are responsible for all actions taken with your login information and password. In case you reveal any login information to the third party you may lose control over your PII and may become a subject to legally binding actions taken on your behalf. So if you assume that your password is not safe and revealed to a third party, dont hesitate to change it.  

  8. Other Information Collectors

This Privacy Policy covers only the relations that appear between users and our website and deals with the information you provide to us only. To the extent that we use third party advertisers or have third party e-commerce partners, they adhere to their own privacy policies. Since we do not control the privacy policies of any third parties, you should investigate their policies before you disclose your personal information to them.  

  9. How we protect your personal information

We take appropriate security measures (including physical, electronic and procedural measures) to protect your personal information from unauthorized access and disclosure. Only authorized employees are permitted to access personal information and they may do so only for permitted business actions. In addition, we use SSL encryption in the transmission of your sensitive personal information between your system and ours, and we use firewalls to help prevent unauthorized users from gaining access to your personal information.  

  10. Adding Changes to the Privacy Policy

We may add changes to this Privacy Policy any moment according to the changes in law, your comments or our need to accurately reflect our data collection and disclosure practices. Certainly, we notify our users about any significant changes by sending a notice via email or by placing a prominent notice on our Site. We recommend that you check our website from time to time to be informed about changes concerning this Privacy Policy or any other policies of our website.  

  11. How to Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information-handling practices, please contact us by email:   

**help at doulike dot com**

© 2009 Ciliara Trading Ltd.  

All rights reserved  

Last Updated August 12, 2009.
